<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Full_Dial xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<dialogs>
		<dial_group id="FirstTest">
			<dial id="welcome">
				<sent>Hello and welcome to this mini visual novel.</sent>
				<sent>I hope you enjoy it.</sent>
				<sent>Well, this is sort of a test, so well, no more to put.</sent>
				<sent>And, now, some explanations. Finished first node.</sent>
			</dial>
				<dial id="Explanation">
				<sent>This visual novel is suposed to be done only by [color=green]Godot's Control nodes [/color] and [color=red]custom c# code[/color].</sent>
				<sent>First, I have an [color=blue]XML[/color] with the text needed. This ways is easy to write the contents, think about the story and write translations.</sent>
				<sent>Then, I have a [color=green]Behaviour Tree[/color] to control the flow. With this, I can create a looooot of scenes that are the little parts of the VN.</sent>
				<sent>For the text, I have the Display system. As I use a custom Entity-Component-System aproximation, the [color=green] Behaviour Tree[/color] nor it's nodes has to worry about it.</sent>
				<sent>So, this intro Scene has 3 [color=green]behaviour tree nodes[/color], 1 for the previous text, 1 for this text and the next for changing the scene.</sent>					
				<sent>And now, I'll change the scene with new nodes, new text!</sent>					
			</dial>	
		</dial_group>
		<dial_group id="SecondTest">
			<dial id="test_a">
				<sent>Ok, now this is the first sentence.</sent>
				<sent>And this is a second sentence.</sent>
				<sent>On this, is the [color=blue]color blue[/color] the protagonist</sent>
				<sent>And now, [color=#517c0c]a custom color[/color] is the protagonist</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="test_b">		
				<sent>Second test. Test pourposes, you know what i mean.</sent>
				<sent>Sentence, sentence, sentence.</sent>
				<sent>Japanese, it works? こんにちは雪子ちゃん、元気ですか。</sent>
				<sent>Spanish, it works? ¿Hola cómo estás, Ñuñí? </sent>
				<sent>Catalonian, it works? Hola, com va, Guèrça? </sent>
				<sent>Esperanto, it works? Saluton, kiel vi fartas, Ĝijŭ? </sent>
				<sent>English, it works? Hello, how are you, Peter? </sent>
				<sent>Thanks for watching! </sent>
			</dial>		
		</dial_group>
		<dial_group id="UNUSED">
			<dial id="believe_ques">
				<sent>Hello, how are you?</sent>
				<sent>Want to make sure that we're on the same page.</sent>
				<sent>Do you believe in Horoscope?</sent>			
			</dial>
			<dial id="believe_yes">
				<sent>Buah, that's amazing, me too.</sent>
				<sent>I expect [color=red]great things[/color] from you.</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="believe_no">
				<sent>Well, I respect that.</sent>
				<sent>I truly wish you good luck.</sent>
			</dial>				
		</dial_group>	
		<dial_group id="ChoiceTest">
			<dial id="choice_test_a">
				<sent>Ok, now it's time to test simple choices.</sent>
				<sent>First we're gonna write this node that ends...</sent>
				<sent>...now!</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="choice_test_b">
				<sent>And this is a second node that also have text...</sent>
				<sent>When making the final game we can simplify all this nodes.</sent>
				<sent>But now is time to test thinks, don't you agree?</sent>
			</dial>		
			<dial id="route_a">
				<sent>That's awesome! We're on the same page!</sent>
				<sent>By the way, this is route A.</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="route_b">
				<sent>Well, I don't really care. You tested the choice selection. Hahahaha</sent>
				<sent>Yes, you guessed right, this is route B.</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="route_c">
				<sent>...</sent>
				<sent>...</sent>
				<sent>I can also play this game if you want. This is route C, in case you care...</sent>
			</dial>
		</dial_group>		
		<dial_group id="BackTest">
			<dial id="empty">
				<sent>empty</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="saluton">
				<sent>Hello, welcome to this new test.</sent>
				<sent>Until now, you only could read and choose some things without further implications.</sent>
				<sent>But that had changed. Now you can move freely in this endless loop that I created.</sent>
				<sent>Truth to be told, I only want to test some things. And... you can't move freely really. So, do you want to come with me?</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="forest">
				<sent>Well, you didn't want to follow me. So, this is the only place that you can go.</sent>
				<sent>You know, there's nothing in here. Well, there's nothing inside this [color=red]life[/color], I think.</sent>
				<sent>You can wait all you want, but there's no hide button so... incomplete, always incomplete...</sent>
				<sent>Want to go back?</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="forest_no">
				<sent>No, you don't really have an option.</sent>
				<sent>The [color=red]future[/color] is already written in a simple [color=green]XML file[/color] and in a [color=blue]Godot scene[/color].</sent>
				<sent>So, you'll start again! [color=black]Hahahahahahaha[/color].</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="forest_yes">
				<sent>Ok, back to the choice!</sent>
				<sent>So, do you want [color=red]NOW[/color] to follow me?</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="back_street">
				<sent>Ok, we are here now. As you can see, there's no much to see.</sent>
				<sent>If you expect some kind of development or some good writing, experience,...</sent>
				<sent>Look at this. All the assets are from the same artist named [color=green]Luis Zuno[/color] from [color=blue]ansimuz.com[/color].</sent>
				<sent>There's no sound, no animations, nothing except the basics onto this world.</sent>
				<sent>Well, basics are important. Don't you agree?</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="back_street_yes_anw">
				<sent>That's good. So, for now and only for your eyes...</sent>
				<sent>[color=green]AN UNPOLISHED AND [color=blue]CUTRE[/color] LOCALIZATION CHANGE![/color]</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="back_street_no_anw">
				<sent>Ok, so, it seems that we disagree on this.</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="back_street_2">
				<sent>It was really really cool, right?</sent>
				<sent>Ok, there's no more choices, no more buttons, no more writting...</sent>
				<sent>I'm tired and I think that this engloves all the testes. Next is to create scenes inside scenes and have a loooooooot of very little scenes.</sent>
				<sent>But, for now, as this [color=red]world[/color] has no exit button, it's time to start again.</sent>
				<sent>Thanks for playing-watching, and have a good day.</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="nothing">
				<sent>Really? You want to start again the scene?</sent>
				<sent>I could ask you a loooooot of time if you're really sure, but...</sent>
				<sent>This is nothing serious, right? Only some test to improve the framework and to act as a game developer or so...</sent>
				<sent>Ok, so it's time to start again!</sent>
				<sent>Fuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu!</sent>
			</dial>
		</dial_group>
		<dial_group id="MusicTest">
			<dial id="Start">
				<sent>Hello again! For todays test, is mandatory that you turn on your speakers.</sent>
				<sent>Yes! That's true! It's time for some BGM.</sent>
				<sent>Right now the world is quiet and in silence. I think is cool, but, some BGM doesn't hurt.</sent>
				<sent>So, I think I'm gonna go with some rain.</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="Rain">
				<sent>All the BGM are from [color=green]opengameart[/color]. The page has a huge selection of free content :D.</sent>
				<sent>This is some rain. Here, in real life, is raining too, but we have some draindrops and not an static image. Hahahaha.</sent>
				<sent>Ok, so now we are going to change for some music.</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="Music">
				<sent>Wooo, it works! I'm proud of you! It looks like you know how to do things! ❤</sent>
				<sent>Ok, the song is from [color=green]opengameart[/color] too. I know that you like music but when is time to make a song is like...</sent>
				<sent>What do you say about some buttons? We have only two tracks though.</sent>
			</dial>
			<dial id="Post_selection">
				<sent>Perfect. I'm too lazy to create a loooot of new nodes.</sent>
				<sent>So, I'm thinking about referencing the choice node and entering an infinity loop.</sent>
				<sent>Why this always turns to be an inifinity loop?</sent>
				<sent>Well, it's a metaphor of your life, maybe?</sent>
				<sent>Don't know and don't wanna know. Make some scripted choices!</sent>
			</dial>
		</dial_group>		
	</dialogs>
	<choices>
		<ch_group id="BackTest">
			<ch id="saluton_ch_a">
				<sent>Yes, I want to come with you.</sent>				
			</ch>
			<ch id="saluton_ch_b">
				<sent>No, I don't really care.</sent>
			</ch>
			<ch id="saluton_ch_c">
				<sent>What? Start again...</sent>
			</ch>
			<ch id="forest_ch_a">
				<sent>Yes, I want to go back.</sent>
			</ch>
			<ch id="forest_ch_b">
				<sent>Have I another option?</sent>
			</ch>	
			<ch id="back_street_yes">
				<sent>Yes, totally!</sent>
			</ch>
			<ch id="back_street_no">
				<sent>Nah, I don't think so</sent>
			</ch>
		
		</ch_group>
		<ch_group id="ChoiceTest">
			<ch id="first_btn">
				<sent>Yes, it's time to check my first choice.</sent>
			</ch>
			<ch id="second_btn">
				<sent>No, I don't want to test.</sent>
			</ch>			
			<ch id="third_btn">
				<sent>...</sent>
			</ch>			
		</ch_group>		
		<ch_group id="MusicTest">
			<ch id="rain_btn">
				<sent>I want to hear the rain!</sent>
			</ch>
			<ch id="track_btn">
				<sent>I want to hear the music track!</sent>
			</ch>
			<ch id="silence_btn">
				<sent>I want some silence!</sent>
			</ch>
		</ch_group>
	</choices>
</Full_Dial>
